

Zerihun Ebbabbu

• Email address: zerihun.ebabu@wku.edu.et

• LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zerihun-ebbabbu-734451131/

YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCenV8eXnp4rPdM3KBafe7rw/featured

• **Upwork:**https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~0105809e838ff702cc?viewMode=1&p=149148408 8808386560

Figma: https://www.figma.com/proto/CNFVluLQ5LY39hBROTkVNP/Mobile--Banking?scaling=scale-down&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=37%3A1431&show-proto-sidebar=1&node-id=37%3A1431

https://www.figma.com/proto/GPHOSVdNCpL1x8nsq2lkYh/Youtube?node-id=1%3A2&scaling=min-zoom&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=1%3A2

Address: Addis Ababa 6 Kilo, 1000 Addis Ababa (Ethiopia)

ABOUT ME

My name is **Zerihun Ebbabbu** and I am a multi-disciplinary UI/UX designer, graphics designer and web developer. I tried to understand the user's problem to bring a better experience for the users. I try to share experiences with other UI/UX designers about how they are going to solve the problems with good professional communication. I have more than two years of experience with design using different designing tools like Adobe families and Figma online platform. This makes me have a good experience in how to solve problems related to my profession.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX and Graphic designer

Girum Technologies [10/07/2020 – 21/07/2022]

Address: Addis Ababa Jemo, 1000 Addis Ababa (Ethiopia) - www.girumtech.com

City: Addis Ababa Country: Ethiopia

My task and responsibility inside Girum Technologies are to design personal and organizational Websites, Mobile apps, booklet, magazine, Stickers, banner, billboard, flyer, label/ package, poster, business card, logo, and certificate design were my main activities in the company.

Graphics Designer

Advanced Digital Printing (ADP) [02/10/2018 – 23/06/2019]

City: Addis Ababa

Country: Ethiopia

My main task and responsibilities when I worked at ADP are to design booklet, magazines, Stickers, banners, billboards, flyers, labels/packages, posters, business cards, logos, and certificate design were my main activities in company.

Graphics Designer (Paid Work)

Wolkite University [23/03/2022 - 27/03/2022]

Address: Wolkite, 07 Wolkite (Ethiopia) - www.wku.edu.et

City: Addis Abeba Country: Ethiopia

Email address: zerihun.ebabu@wku.edu.et

Name of unit or department: Computer Science - Business or sector: Education

Workshop banner, billboard, and flyer for developed software for research and community service.

University Assistant Lecturer

Wolkite University [20/08/2015 - 15/09/2019]

City: Wolkite
Country: Ethiopia

Assistant lecturer at Wolkite University. The main activities are delivering lectures and assisting students when they are developing software. In addition to this, I was trying to develop a student information management system (SIMS) as a community service.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

BSc Degree in Computer Science (University Degree) Wolkite University [17/11/2012 - 12/07/2015]

Address: Wolkite, 07 Wolkite (Ethiopia) www.wku.edu.et

Videography and Photography TVET

Tom Training Center [23/02/2019 – 23/02/2020]

Address: Addis Ababa Piazza, Inside Taitu Hotel's Compound, 1000 Addis Ababa (Ethiopia) https://tomtrainingcenter.com/

Graphics Design Training

BERHANENA SELAM PRINTING [10/01/2019 – 24/06/2019]

Address: Addis Ababa 4 Kilo, 1000 Addis Ababa (Ethiopia) https://ethbspe.org/en_US/about-us/background/

Certificate of Completion

ICSI [10/02/2020 - 29/06/2020] Address: UK

Online, https://icsiglobal.com/

IT essentials (Certificate of Training)

CISCO [01/02/2014 – 30/06/2015]

Address: Wolkite, 07 Wolkite (Ethiopia)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Amharic Other

language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Figma, Adobe (Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premier PRO) / Language (C#, Java, C++, PHP, .NET framework, React JS)

Figma practical activities

(Portfolio)

- https://www.figma.com/proto/YVJObG3tUZPjFNfqrNsIry/Telegram?scaling=scale-down&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=10%3A21&show-proto-sidebar=1&node-id=114%3A6
- https://www.figma.com/proto/GPHOSVdNCpL1x8nsq2lkYh/Youtube?node-id=1%3A2&scaling=min-zoom&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=1%3A2
- https://www.figma.com/proto/NWC7eJlzcTWAW6t0aaKdJF/Binance-Mobile-app?scaling=scale-down&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=0%3A94&node-id=0%3A82
- <a href="https://www.figma.com/proto/CNFVluLQ5LY39hBROTkVNP/Mobile--Banking?scaling=scale-down&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=37%3A1431&show-proto-sidebar=1&node-id=37%3A1431
- https://www.figma.com/proto/ZACaABmRbTdTwNOV3aNBoA/Facebook-pro?scaling=scale-down&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=2%3A243

Adobe designs portfolio

https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~0105809e838ff702cc